[
    {
        "categoria": "Match the sentences",
        "pregunta": "Bespoke",
        "respuesta": "specially produced for someone",
        "incorrecta1": "errors in a program",
        "incorrecta2": "final move to a new system",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Match the sentences",
        "pregunta": "Bugs",
        "respuesta": "errors in a program",
        "incorrecta1": "specially produced for someone",
        "incorrecta2": "final move to a new system",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Match the sentences",
        "pregunta": "Cutover",
        "respuesta": "final move to a new system",
        "incorrecta1": "in separate, independent sections",
        "incorrecta2": "standard and commercially",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Match the sentences",
        "pregunta": "Modular",
        "respuesta": "in separate, independent sections",
        "incorrecta1": "final move to a new system",
        "incorrecta2": "standard and commercially",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Match the sentences",
        "pregunta": "Off the shelf",
        "respuesta": "standard and commercially",
        "incorrecta1": "final move to a new system",
        "incorrecta2": "in separate, independent sections",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Match the sentences",
        "pregunta": "Output",
        "respuesta": "work finished or completed",
        "incorrecta1": "strong, reliabe",
        "incorrecta2": "gradual implementation",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Match the sentences",
        "pregunta": "Robust",
        "respuesta": "strong, reliabe",
        "incorrecta1": "work finished or completed",
        "incorrecta2": "gradual implementation",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Match the sentences",
        "pregunta": "Rollout",
        "respuesta": "gradual implementation",
        "incorrecta1": "strong, reliabe",
        "incorrecta2": "work finished or completed",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Match the sentences",
        "pregunta": "Sign off",
        "respuesta": "finish and leave",
        "incorrecta1": "detailed description of what is required",
        "incorrecta2": "small and medium-sized enterprises",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Match the sentences",
        "pregunta": "SME",
        "respuesta": "small and medium-sized enterprises",
        "incorrecta1": "finish and leave",
        "incorrecta2": "detailed description of what is required",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Match the sentences",
        "pregunta": "Specification",
        "respuesta": "detailed description of what is required",
        "incorrecta1": "finish and leave",
        "incorrecta2": "small and medium-sized enterprises",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    },

    {
        "categoria": "Match the sentences",
        "pregunta": "Steady state",
        "respuesta": "working properly",
        "incorrecta1": "small and medium-sized enterprises",
        "incorrecta2": "detailed description of what is required",
        "imagen": "",
        "objectFit": "cover"
    }
]